convertzone.com 2008-09-17

# Create PDF,convert PDF to TEXT,WORD DOC to PDF,HTML to PDF,RTF to PDF,XLS to PDF,PPT to PDF,support batch conversion

**Category:**

|  PDF|  Word| Spreadsheet| PowerPoint| Database| CAD| Email Chat&News| Audio| Video| Image| Help| XML  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
## Privacy Policy (Sept 3, 2000)

ConvertZone understands the need for security and privacy and is committed to using every reasonable means to protect its customers. ConvertZone has published this Privacy Policy to answer basic questions regarding the policy; if you require more detailed information, please address your question(s) in an email to: [privacy@convertzone.com](mailto:privacy@convertzone.com). All questions will be responded to within 2 working days.

From time to time, certain aspects of our Privacy Policy may be modified. Thus, our Privacy Policy will always be dated; if and when a fundamental change is made in our privacy policy, notification to that effect will be posted on the home page of [www.convertzone.com](http://www.convertzone.com/), and will remain in place for a minimum of one month after the policy change.

ConvertZone desires to provide customers with a pleasant, worry free shopping experience. Towards that end, ConvertZone uses encryption technologies and secure databases to jealously protect the privacy and security of its customers. ConvertZone collects information from customers for the following purposes, and collects only the minimum information required for these purposes:

  * To accurately and safely process credit card transactions 
  * To provide updated product information and/or newsletters and bulletins if specifically requested by the customer.

At no time will ConvertZone provide customer information to third parties, and at no time will ConvertZone send emails or other information to customers without the customer's consent. For example, ConvertZone will send newsletters only to customers who request the newsletter, and will provide these customers with a simple and easy method to unsubscribe at their desire.

Access to secure databases and customer information at ConvertZone is tightly controlled; only a few certain individuals are allowed access to customer information, and then only as the demands of their work require it.

If you would like any further information regarding ConvertZone's Privacy Policy, please contact us to [privacy@convertzone.com](mailto:privacy@convertzone.com).
